Guide to International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousmen and Helpers of America records: digital edition produced from microfilm, 1904-1952 LAC0004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General correspondence, 1907-1952; Series 5; 8 microfilm reels
  - U.S. - National Mediation Board, 1941-1943, 1948-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 5)
  - U.S. - National Railroad Adjustment Board, Series 5 (Reel 86)
    See: Luhrsen, J. G.
  - U.S. - National Recovery Administration, 1935; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 6)
  - U.S. - Navy, Department of the, 1942-1943, 1949-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 7)
  - U.S. - Post Office, 1907-1908, 1941-1946; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 8)
  - U.S. - President's Highway Safety Conference, 1947, 1949; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 9)
  - U.S. - President's National Labor - Management Conference, 1945; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 10)
  - U.S. - Price Administration, Office of, 1942-1946; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 11)
  - U.S. - Railroad Retirement Board, 1944-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 12)
  - U.S. - State, Department of, 1941-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 13)
  - U.S. - Treasury Department, 1938-1952; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 14)
  - U.S. - Veterans Administration, 1946; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 15)
  - U.S. - War, Department of, 1941-1947; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 16)
  - United States News, 1941-1947; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 17)
  - United Truck Owners, 1942-1943, 1949-1951; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 18)
  - Universities and Students, 1920-1922, 1940-1947; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 19)
  - Universities and Students, 1948-1949; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 20)
  - Universities and Students, 1950; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 21)
  - Universities and Students, 1951-1952, undated; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 22)
  - Ua - Uz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 23)
  - Virginia Engineering Company, 1945-1947; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 24)
  - Va - Vz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 25)
  - Walling, William English, 1924; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 26)
  - Watson, Edwin M., 1940-1944; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 27)
  - Wolf, Robert B., 1922-1924, 1940-1941; Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 28)
  - Wa, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 29)
  - Wb - Wh, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 30)
  - Wi - Wz, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 31)
  - X - Z, miscellaneous, Series 5 (Reel 86, Segment 32)
- Retakes, 1905-1952; Series 6; 1 microfilm reels (Reel 87, Segment 1-86)
  1-86 Retakes. (Index numbers correspond to the reels on which the filming errors were made. For instance, if you are using Reel 71 and come to a frame with a hole punched in it, indicating a filming error, you can find the correction at index number 71 on Reel 87.)
  Arranged chronologically by reel number.
  - Reel 1, 1910-1952; Series 6 (Reel 87, Segment 1)
  - Reel 2, 1907-1950; Series 6 (Reel 87, Segment 2)
  - Reel 3, 1917-1926 (Reel 87, Segment 3)
  - Reel 4, 1908-1947 (Reel 87, Segment 4)
  - Reel 5, 1914-1927 (Reel 87, Segment 5)
  - Reel 6, 1912-1937 (Reel 87, Segment 6)
  - Reel 7, 1919-1934 (Reel 87, Segment 7)
  - Reel 8, 1926-1950 (Reel 87, Segment 8)
  - Reel 9, 1914-1922 (Reel 87, Segment 9)
  - Reel 10, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 10)
  - Reel 11, 1907-1950 (Reel 87, Segment 11)
  - Reel 12, 1908-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 12)
  - Reel 13, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 13)
  - Reel 14, 1908-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 14)
  - Reel 15, 1923-1949 (Reel 87, Segment 15)
  - Reel 16, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 16)
  - Reel 17, 1910-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 17)
  - Reel 18, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 18)
  - Reel 19, 1914-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 19)
  - Reel 20, 1919-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 20)
  - Reel 21, 1935-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 21)
  - Reel 22, 1910-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 22)
  - Reel 23, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 23)
  - Reel 24, 1942-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 24)
  - Reel 25, 1933-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 25)
  - Reel 26, 1927-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 26)
  - Reel 27, 1919-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 27)
  - Reel 28, 1921-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 28)
  - Reel 29, 1914-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 29)
  - Reel 30, 1912-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 30)
  - Reel 31, 1930-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 31)
  - Reel 32, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 32)
  - Reel 33, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 33)
  - Reel 34, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 34)
  - Reel 35, 1917-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 35)
  - Reel 36, 1920-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 36)
  - Reel 37, 1910-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 37)
  - Reel 38, 1932-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 38)
  - Reel 39, 1910-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 39)
  - Reel 40, 1918-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 40)
  - Reel 41, 1925-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 41)
  - Reel 42, 1913-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 42)
  - Reel 43, 1913-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 43)
  - Reel 44, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 44)
  - Reel 45, 1917-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 45)
  - Reel 46, 1914-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 46)
  - Reel 47, 1917-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 47)
  - Reel 48, 1916-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 48)
  - Reel 49, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 49)
  - Reel 50, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 50)
  - Reel 51, 1938-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 51)
  - Reel 52, 1938-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 52)
  - Reel 53, 1940-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 53)
  - Reel 54, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 54)
  - Reel 55, 1942-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 55)
  - Reel 56, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 56)
  - Reel 57, 1914-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 57)
  - Reel 58, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 58)
  - Reel 59, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 59)
  - Reel 60, 1940-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 60)
  - Reel 61, 1942-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 61)
  - Reel 62, 1943-1949 (Reel 87, Segment 62)
  - Reel 63, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 63)
  - Reel 64, 1941-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 64)
  - Reel 65, 1905-1924 (Reel 87, Segment 65)
  - Reel 66, 1924-1927 (Reel 87, Segment 66)
  - Reel 67, 1928-1935 (Reel 87, Segment 67)
  - Reel 68, 1936-1939 (Reel 87, Segment 68)
  - Reel 69, 1939-1942 (Reel 87, Segment 69)
  - Reel 70, 1943-1947 (Reel 87, Segment 70)
  - Reel 71, 1923-1937 (Reel 87, Segment 71)
  - Reel 72, 1938-1945 (Reel 87, Segment 72)
  - Reel 73, 1946-1951 (Reel 87, Segment 73)
  - Reel 74, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 74)
  - Reel 75, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 75)
  - Reel 76, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 76)
  - Reel 77, 1916-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 77)
  - Reel 78 (Reel 87, Segment 78)
  - Reel 79, 1919-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 79)
  - Reel 80, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 80)
  - Reel 81, 1908-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 81)
  - Reel 82, 1921-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 82)
  - Reel 83, 1939-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 83)
  - Reel 84, 1923-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 84)
  - Reel 85, 1935-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 85)
  - Reel 86, 1907-1952 (Reel 87, Segment 86)